Pray for Day
Night of the Wild is a horror, tv movie film directed by Eric Red.
A large meteor crashes into a quiet town, and pet
dogs become mysteriously aggressive.
attacking and killing the residents.
Teenager Roslyn and her old but faithful dog Shep
are out camping when the attacks hit.
Now separated by the chaos in town and blocked roads, Roslyn and the other members of her family must find each other by
fighting back against the blood-thirsty hounds before the dogs take over the whole town and escape becomes impossible.
Dave, played by Rob Morrow.
Sara, played by Kelly Rutherford.
Rosalyn, played by Tristin Mays.
Danielle, played by Carmen Tonry.
Liz, played by Jill Zarin.
Pia, played by Mary Risener.
Night of the Wild is a 2015 American television science fiction horror
film directed by Eric Red and written by Delondra Williams.
The film premiered on Syfy on October 3, 2015.
The film explores themes of small town, animal attack, meteor, dog, killer dog.
The tone is dark.